<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rows>
    <row>
        <title>Decathlon</title>
        <text>DECATHLON is a French company created more than 40 years ago operating in 50+ countries in the world. In
            Russia, you will join a team of 3 000 dynamic, young and sportive persons. The objective of Decathlon is to
            make sports available to the many.
            Decathlon is a strong actor on worldwide sport’s market grows continuously, we develops our own brands and
            sells sports products, which are exclusively available in DECATHLON stores.

            In Russia, DECATHLON operates through 55 + stores and also do local production selling mostly our own
            products in our stores and online, we have a clear wish to expand throughout the country.

            Decathlon offers horizontal management which gives real freedom for your projects and responsibility.
            LEAD FULL STACK (JAVA) DEVELOPER
            Decathlon Russia is looking for a high-skill full-stack developer with good skills in Java EE.

            RESPONSIBILITIES:
            Work on development of company internal and external projects.
            Advise technical solutions
            Work on projects with others developers and outsourced developers teams
            Review technical specifications
            Work on planning sprint and releases
            Help to improve performance, review, modify and refine solutions within and outside of the team to enhance
            performance metrics and standards
            Solve challenging problems
            REQUIREMENTS AND SKILLS:
            High knowledge of Java EE development (Spring, JSP)
            Ability to develop frontend as a plus
            DB PostgreSQL (DB Oracle as a plus)
            Experience in API creation, management
            Experience in micro-service architecture
            Server management and architecture as a plus
            ADDITIONAL SKILS:
            Have an entrepreneurial mindset
            Strong management/communication skills
            Be able to explain simply technical decisions to non-expert
            Be proactive and innovative
            Intermediate English
            WE PROPOSE:
            Young ambitious team with friendly atmosphere
            Competitive salary + Bonus
            Medical and life insurance
            Opportunity to become a shareholder
            Discount 20% on Decathlon goods
            Office in Altufievo. April of 2019 movement in Park Legend.
            Отправляя отклик на данную вакансию, данным действием я предоставляю ООО «ОКТОБЛУ», ИНН 5029086747, 141031,
            Российская Федерация, Московская область, Мытищинский район, 84км МКАД, ТПЗ «Алтуфьево», владение 3,
            строение 3 (Оператор персональных данных) для целей возможного моего трудоустройства в компанию ООО
            «ОКТОБЛУ» своё согласие в соответствии с Федеральным законом от 27.07.2006г. № 152-ФЗ «О персональных
            данных» осуществлять со всеми указанными в моем резюме персональными данными, а также с самим резюме
            следующие действия: систематизацию, накопление, хранение, уточнение (обновление/изменение), использование,
            обезличивание, блокирование и уничтожение. Также даю свое согласие на передачу (в том числе трансграничную)
            моих персональных данных. Я уведомлен, что мои персональные данные могут обрабатываться в странах, которые
            не обеспечивают адекватную защиту персональных данных.
            Настоящее согласие на обработку персональных данных мною предоставляется без ограничения срока обработки
            этих персональных данных, но до момента отзыва согласия. Настоящее согласие может быть отозвано путем
            направления соответствующего заявления Оператору персональных данных по адресу: 141031, Российская
            Федерация, Московская область, Мытищинский район, 84км МКАД, ТПЗ «Алтуфьево», владение 3, строение 3.
            &lt;!-- --&gt;Ключевые навыки
            Java
            Agile Project Management
            Английский язык
            PostgreSQL
            Project management
            Spring FrameworkАдрес
            Алтуфьево, Москва, МКАД, 84-й километр, вл3с3
            ­
            © Яндекс Условия использованияВакансия опубликована 29 января 2019 в Москве
            Отклик на вакансию
            Продолжить
            Быстрое создание резюме через соцсеть
            Уже зарегистрированы?
            Войти
            Нажимая «Продолжить», вы подтверждаете, что ознакомлены, полностью согласны и принимаете условия «Соглашения
            об оказании услуг по содействию в трудоустройстве (оферта)»Вакансии из других профобластей
            Информационные технологии, интернет, телеком
            Банковское ПО
            Программирование, Разработка
            Стартапы
        </text>
        <salary>0</salary>
        <metro>Алтуфьево, Москва, МКАД, 84-й километр, вл3с3Алтуфьево, Москва, МКАД, 84-й километр, вл3с3</metro>
        <years>1</years>
    </row>
</rows>